24seventalent.com 2017-12-27

# 24 SEVEN PRIVACY POLICY | 24Seven Talent

This is the privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) for the sites operated by 24 Seven LLC and its affiliated entities (“24 Seven,” “we,” “us,” “our”) in the United States (the “US Sites”) and the United Kingdom (the “UK Site” and together with the US Sites and various related services collectively referred to herein as the “Sites”).  The Sites include those located at [www.24seveninc.com](http://www.24seveninc.com/),  [www.24seventalent.com](http://www.24seventalent.com/) and [www.24seveninc.co.uk](http://www.24seveninc.co.uk/).   

The US Sites are owned and operated by 24 Seven LLC, a Delaware limited liability company with offices located at 120 Wooster Street, 4th Floor, New York, NY 10012.  The UK Site is operated by 24 Seven LLC and owned by 24 Seven UK Limited, a U.K. company (registered company number 6128695) located at 1st Floor, 65-66 Dean Street, London, W10 4QH and whose registered office is at 5 New Street Square, London EC4A 3TW.

This Privacy Policy sets forth our policies regarding the collection, use, disclosure, sharing, transfer, and/or deletion of certain information relating to you and your use of the Sites. Your use of the Sites signifies your understanding and acceptance of the terms of this Privacy Policy.  This Privacy Policy is hereby incorporated into, and made a part of, the applicable terms and conditions of use of the Sites (the “Terms of Use”), which govern your use of the Sites, in general.

WE UNDERSTAND HOW IMPORTANT YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION IS TO YOU AND WE RESPECT YOUR PRIVACY.  ANY INFORMATION GATHERED BY US ABOUT YOU ON THE SITES WILL BE PROTECTED IN ACCORDANCE WITH THIS PRIVACY POLICY AS APPLICABLE.  UNLESS WE HAVE YOUR CONSENT, WE WILL NOT SHARE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION TO ANY NON-AFFILIATED THIRD PARTY EXCEPT AS OTHERWISE PERMITTED IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY.

**Age Requirement**.

You must have reached the age of majority in the jurisdiction in which you live to have our permission to use this site.  Our policy is that we do not knowingly collect, use or disclose personally identifiable information about visitors that are under the age of majority.

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act), and we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age.  Our website and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

**Collection and Use of Your Personal Information**.

You may visit the Sites without providing us with any of your personal information, but some of the services that we make available through the Sites require that you provide us with certain personal information such as your name, physical address, e-mail and Web site address(es) and phone number(s).  In addition, we may ask you to provide us information regarding your citizenship, your employment and career requirements and preferences, your skills, experience, salary history and other similar information.  For example, you will not be able to enjoy certain benefits we offer unless you become a member of our talent pool by registering within our Sites (such site(s) of registration and participation being referred to herein as the “Talent Site”) by providing the personal information that we request in the [registration](http://24seveninc.com/en-us/sign-up/) section.  If you do not provide the mandatory data with respect to a particular benefit or activity, you will not be able to engage in that activity and/or gain such benefit.

By providing us with your personal information when you become a member of the Talent Site you expressly consent to our using such information to: (i) provide you with services in connection with our operations as an employment/recruitment agency, (ii) contact you about your membership account or account activity (including, without limitation, setting up interviews with our recruitment specialists or potential employers), (iii) send you information about the benefits of the Talent Site membership (including, without limitation, our and our affiliates' and business partners' products and services, unless you have opted out of receiving any such information), and (iv) in aggregated form only, to market and promote the Sites and our business generally (for example, to inform current and potential clients regarding the number of job seekers with specific technical abilities who have posted their resumes on the Talent Site).

Rest assured that we only collect, use and share that personal information that you voluntarily and knowingly submit to us through the Sites.

**Collection and Use of Technical (Non-Personally-Identifiable) Information**.

When you visit the Sites, we may also collect technical information that does not, by itself, identify you as a specific individual.  This information (sometimes referred to as “non-personally identifiable information”) may include the address of the Web site that you came from before visiting one of the Sites, which pages you visit on the Sites, which browser you use to view the Sites and, if search functionality is available on the Site, any search terms that you may have entered.  We may also collect your IP (Internet Protocol) address an IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer, so Web servers can automatically identify individual computers by their IP address - to help diagnose problems with our servers, administer the Sites, see where the traffic on the Sites is coming from or identify you as the user of a particular computer.  Such collection of information also applies to your mobile device, such as its unique device identifier.  We may also collect other non-personally identifiable information via the Sites, such as the Site's usage activity and preferences, also known as demographic or profile data.  We may match information collected from you through different means or at different times, and use such information along with information obtained from other sources, including third parties.  We do not intend to combine this technical data with your personally-identifiable information, but we reserve the right to do so.  We will use the information that you provide to us solely in accordance with the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy.

**How We Use “Cookies” and Other Technologies**.

“Cookies” are small pieces of information that some Web sites store on your computer's hard drive when you visit their Web sites.  Like many other Web sites, we use cookies on the Sites, for example, to identify you as a registered user of the Talent Site so that you do not have to re-enter your personal information upon each visit.  Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies but allow you to modify security settings so you can approve or reject cookies on a case-by-case basis.  Like other Web sites, we may also use other tracking technologies (for example, Web bugs, e-mail bugs, clear GIFs, Web beacons, or tracker GIFs) in the Sites and in our communications with you to enhance the functionality of the Sites and to make your interactions and other activities more convenient and efficient.

**What We May Share With or Otherwise Provide to Third Parties**.

We do not provide access to your personal information to third parties except as set forth in this Privacy Policy.

If we believe that your qualifications match certain job postings or general needs of our clients, we may share your resume with them, but the resume we disclose to them will have your name, address, phone number, fax number, and e-mail address deleted and replaced with the address and other contact information of 24 Seven.

In addition, we may provide third parties with aggregate statistics about traffic patterns, and related site information.  This data reflects site usage patterns gathered during our users' visits to the Sites, but it does not contain behavioral, profile, or identifying information about any personally identified individual user.  By using the Sites, you give us permission to collect information about the pages served to you as an anonymous user for the purpose of calculating aggregate site statistics.  If you become a registered member of the Talent Site, you authorize us to use the information you provide there to personalize the information we deliver to you and to use your demographic information when calculating aggregate user data.

Except as provided above, or as required by applicable law, regulations, or court order, or to protect or defend our rights or the rights or well-being of our users, or if you are involved (or are reasonably suspected to be involved) in any illegal activity, even without a subpoena, warrant or court order, or in connection with the sale of substantially all the assets of 24 Seven or its merger, reorganization, consolidation or liquidation, or in connection with specific services that you have requested from us and that we have agreed to provide but may be providing through third parties, or pursuant to your express prior consent, we will not share with or disclose to third parties the personal information we collect from you through the Sites.

**Postings and Public Areas**.

You are solely responsible for the information and other content you post on or through the Sites.  You understand that personal and other information (such as your name, e-mail address, phone number) that you post on or through public areas of the Sites, if any, are generally accessible to, and may be collected and used by, others and may result in unsolicited messages or other contact from others.  We encourage you to exercise caution when providing personal information about you on any public areas of the Sites, if any such areas are made available.

If you elect to use our referral service to inform a third party about the Sites, or if you otherwise provide a third party's personal information to us or to the Sites, you warrant that you have permission to do so and you agree to indemnify, defend and hold us and our affiliates harmless from and against any claim, liability, cost and expense (including attorney’s fees) arising in any way there from.

**Third Party Advertisements; Links to Third Party Sites**.

The Sites may contain advertisements placed by third parties on the Sites, or links to third party Web sites.  For example, many of the benefits that you can access by becoming a member of the Talent Site are available directly from such third parties.  The personal information we collect from you on the Sites is not shared by us with such third parties, unless we specifically tell you otherwise on a case-by-case basis.  In order to take advantage of such benefits, you will have to go directly to the Web sites of the companies that provide such benefits, and provide them with whatever information they request and whatever information you wish to voluntarily provide to them.

Just like we do, the third parties who place advertisements on the Sites may use cookies, Web beacons and other tracking technologies to collect your information when you click on their advertisements, and each of the linked third party Web sites have their own information collection and use practices and policies.  We have no control over what information such third parties may track or collect, how they conduct their tracking or collection, or how they use the information they track or collect, and we assume no responsibility or liability for any tracking, data collection or other activities of any such third parties.  Before you provide them with your personal information, please make sure that you have read and understood their privacy policies (and that you are also familiar and understand their specific Web site terms and conditions of use).  YOU HEREBY ACKNOWLEDGE AND AGREE THAT THIS PRIVACY POLICY DOES NOT GOVERN ANY THIRD PARTY'S PRIVACY PRACTICES.

**Opting Out**.

Our users are generally given the opportunity to “opt-out” of having their information used for purposes not directly related to the Sites at the point where we ask for information.

Notwithstanding the above, your option not to receive promotional and marketing material shall not preclude us from corresponding with you, by e-mail or otherwise, regarding your existing or past relationship with us (such as, for example, your Talent Site membership activity, your request that we grant you an interview, or that we place you in a job, or our responses to questions or inquiries you pose to us), and shall not preclude us from accessing and viewing your personal information in the course of maintaining and improving the Sites and generally conducting our employment/recruitment business.

**Special Offers, Newsletter**.

Established members of the Talent Site may occasionally receive information on products, services, special deals, other promotional announcements, surveys and our newsletter.  Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present you with the option to not receive these types of communications in the future.

**Service Announcements**.

On rare occasions it is necessary to send out a strictly service related announcement that is not promotional in nature.  For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send users an e-mail.  Generally, you may not opt-out of these communications, though you may always deactivate (cancel) your Talent Site membership, in which case you will no longer receive such service announcements.

**Security**.

Any personal data you enter on the Sites when becoming a member of the Talent Site, or through any other means or communications with us, is collected and stored in a database.  We will take reasonable precautions to protect your personal information from loss, misuse or alteration.  Only authorized 24 Seven employees and agents have access to the data.  24 Seven employees and agents will not share information with any third parties outside 24 Seven, other than as set forth in this Privacy Policy or in connection with a specific company with whom you have authorized us to conduct discussions regarding your potential placement.

We use a variety of safeguards to protect your sensitive information from loss, misuse, alteration or destruction.  Notwithstanding the above, due to the open nature of the Internet, we cannot guarantee that any information stored on our servers, or transmitted to or from a user, will be free from unauthorized access.  By using the Sites, you acknowledge that (i) there are security and privacy limitations of the Internet which are beyond our control; (ii) the security, integrity and privacy of any and all information and data exchanged between you and us through this site cannot be guaranteed; and (iii) any such information and data may be viewed or tampered with in transit by a third party.

Please be careful whenever you send personal information to us via e-mail.  E-mail is commonly not a secure means of transferring information.

**Access to Your Information; Making Corrections, Changes; Deactivating Your personal Information**.

If at any time you wish to find out what personal information we hold about you in our databases, or you wish to access, correct, change, update or delete that information, you may do so by logging onto the Talent Site and following the instructions.

**Consent to Processing**.

By providing any personal information to us through any of the Sites, you fully understand and unambiguously consent to the transfer of such personal information to, and the collection and processing of such personal information in, the United States and other countries or territories.

**Notification of Changes**.

We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time. Such changes, modifications, additions or deletions shall be effective immediately upon notice thereof.  In the event our Privacy Policy should change, we will post those changes on the Privacy Policy Web page, with a notice thereof on the homepage of the applicable Site, and in any other places we deem appropriate so you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

In general, we will use information in accordance with the version of the Privacy Policy under which the information was collected.  If, however, we decide to use or disclose your personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection, we will generally notify you via e-mail prior to such use or disclosure of any such information.  You will have the opportunity to opt-out of any change in the use of your information by e-mailing us at [membership@24seventalent.com](mailto:membership@24seventalent.com).  However, if you have opted out of all communication with the Sites (including Talent Site), or deleted/deactivated your membership account with the Talent Site, then you will not be contacted, nor will your personal information be used or disclosed in this new manner.  Notwithstanding anything to the contrary above, if we make any material changes in our privacy practices that do not affect user information already stored in our database, we will merely post a prominent notice on the Sites notifying you of the change.  You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review the Sites and this Privacy Policy periodically and to be aware of any modifications.  Your continued use of the Sites following the posting of changes means your acceptance of those changes.

**Applicable Law**.

The Sites are governed solely by applicable U.S. laws and governmental regulations. Use of this site constitutes your consent to application of such laws and regulations and to our Privacy Policy.

**California Privacy Rights**

California Civil Code Section 1798.83, also known as the “Shine The Light” law, permits California residents who provide personal information (as defined in the statute) in obtaining services from us to request and obtain from us once a year, free of charge, information about the personally identifiable information (if any) we disclosed to third parties for marketing purposes in the preceding calendar year.  If applicable, this information would include a list of the categories of personal information that was shared and the names and addresses of all third parties with which we shared information in the immediately preceding calendar year.  If you are a California resident and would like to make such a request, please submit your request in writing to 24 Seven LLC, Attention: Legal 120 Wooster Street, 4th Floor, New York, NY 10012.  Please be aware that not all information sharing is covered by the “Shine the Light” requirements, and only information on covered sharing will be included in our response.

**Questions or Comments?**

If you have any questions or comments about our information collection, use or sharing practices, or about how this Privacy Policy works, please e-mail us at [legal@24seventalent.com](mailto:legal@24seventalent.com), write us at 24 Seven LLC, Attention: Legal 120 Wooster Street, 4th Floor, New York, NY 10012 or call us at [212-966-4426](tel:212-966-4426).
